The wedding invitations have been sent out.
Do you want
to ruin the reputation of the Ling family
and the Ye family in Yang City?
If the marriage of the Ling family
needs to rely on a girl to maintain,
then we don't need the reputation.
How dare you!
Marriage is a serious matter.
It's up to the parents
and the matchmaker.
You have no say in it.
I was indeed too rude.
I'll go reflect.
You...
Young Marshal,
everything's been arranged.
Xueqiu's documents,
school, and property are all set.
Pick her up at the back door tomorrow morning.
Ye Wenbo killed people in the street.
I've put him in jail.
OK.
Since you decided to send Miss Xueqiu abroad,
you've been doing everything by yourself.
Why don't you have a rest?
Forgive me for being so frank.
Although the Ye family is not a good match,
why do you
have to send Miss Xueqiu abroad?
Why don't you find another good husband for her?
I want to put an end to her idea.
I did have this intention,
but the Old Madam was too persistent,
so I had to take this approach.
Although the Ye family is the Old Madam's maternal family,
the status of women is low.
I think if Xueqiu marries into that family,
there could be hidden dangers.
Besides,
an eagle that has seen the sky
wouldn't be willing to be confined to the backyard
in the backyard?
You let her choose
literature, art, law,
and architecture.
Isn't it too much
for a woman?
People think so
because they think
a woman's only way out is marriage.
Xueqiu wants to learn architecture
because she wants to know
can support a large building.
She wants to study law
because she wants to know
how to protect fairness
by rules.
Men can learn these,
why can't women?
I don't want
gender to stop her from seeing a bigger world.
If she doesn't want to get married in the future,
her ability
will be her greatest asset.
Compared to relying on others,
the hardships of studying
are nothing.
Xueqiu wants to study abroad.
I've agreed to her.
After dinner,
we'll go to the station to see her off.
Really?
She can finally get away
from the person she dislikes.
Just like you
wanted to get rid of me?
So,
are you jealous?
You knew we ran away
at that time?
Of course.
Otherwise, how could I find you so fast?
This is from the kids in the orphanage.
They asked me to give it to you.
You said
people do things for a purpose.
So, Ling Shenxing,
why did you build an orphanage?
Of course,
it's for fame and fortune.
The kids at the orphanage said
you never show up,
just send things over.
Even Abao,
if I hadn't seen your signature,
I wouldn't have known
for Abao's medical bills.
I really underestimated you.
You even know about Abao.
Of course.
Who do you think I am?
If I hadn't been falsely accused,
I would have found Abao long ago.
During this time,
I've heard a lot of things.
Everyone has their own story,
but the one thing they all agree on is
everyone says
Commander Ling
and Young Marshal
are the pillars of Yang City.
With you,
Yang City is safe.
And,
I found something interesting.
Close your eyes.
Open them.
Ling Shenxing,
do you like me?
My Lady,
what if I do?
This is my answer.
This is...
Commander Ling.
Ah.
This is my father
and his aide-de-camp.
Is the aide-de-camp missing?
This
was found on my father's body.
I've confirmed with Hongxiu.
This is the heirloom jade pendant of the Su family,
and it's only passed down to the head of the family.
So you suspect
my father killed your father?
At first, I suspected.
But then the Su family was accused of hiding prohibited drugs.
It's all too coincidental.
Clearly, someone set this up.
I want to see Hongxiu.
This sachet,
is it made just for me,
or for many people?
I made several,
but this one
is the most delicate.
If you don't like it,
I'll tear it up.
Don't make it for anyone else.
We're here.
Hongxiu,
I must find out the truth of that night.
Go in.
Xiao Wan,
long time no see.
Chu Nanfeng,
why is he here?
You go in first.
I'm here.
What are you doing?
Move inside.
Go back.
Hongxiu.
What's your show today?
Young Marshal Ling.
Why did you bring Xiao Wan here?
Chu Nanfeng.
Mind your own business.
I know what you're thinking.
You come to the prison with so many people.
I have to come and see
if you're really interrogating the prisoner
or to trick Wan?
Ling Shenxing,
I've always been tolerant,
but this time,
I won't tolerate it anymore.
Su Muwan,
I'm determined to have her.
My lady.
Hongxiu,
you've suffered a lot.
Miss.
I'm dirty.
Don't get your clothes dirty.
I didn't take care of you well.
When I heard you were in trouble,
I was sad.
I didn't expect
that you were safe
and sound.
Don't be sad.
We will all be fine.
Hongxiu,
I can't remember some things before the accident.
Why were you locked up?
At first, it was because
I tried to kill the Third Madame.
The Third Madame?
Is there a Third Madame in the Ling residence?
Yes, there is.
My lady, don't you remember?
The Third Madame's courtyard
is filled with lilacs.
I heard that lilac sachets can repel mosquitoes.
When you were marching and fighting,
you often suffered from mosquito bites.
So you ordered me to make a lilac sachet for you.
That day,
I went with you
to visit the Third Madame
with the perfume you made.
The Third Madame
liked the perfume very much.
She immediately poured some on her wrist.
But she died
shortly after.
Has this perfume
been handled by anyone else?
I remember the Second Madame's maid smelled it
and praised your skills.
Second Madame, I forgot about you.
By the way,
do you remember who has the Su family's jade pendant?
When you got married,
the Master gave you
the jade pendant.
Did I give it to someone else?
I'm not sure.
[Hongxiu,]
[hold on a little longer.]
[I will get you out of there.]